<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Overwatch Beta Patches</title><link>http://jbzdarkid.github.io/feed.rss</link><description>A Github-hosted RSS feed for the Overwatch Forums</description><atom:link href="http://jbzdarkid.github.io/feed.rss" rel="self"/><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>http://us.battle.net/forums/static/images/logos/logo-small-overwatch.png</url><title>Overwatch Beta Patches</title><link>http://jbzdarkid.github.io/feed.rss</link></image><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2016 13:08:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Overwatch Patch Notes - June 14, 2016</title><description>A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn more about the latest changes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813879/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;General Discussion &lt;/a&gt;forum.&lt;br/&gt;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813881/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813880/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note that many of these changes will be rolled into a larger patch for PlayStation 4 and Xbox One at a later date. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HERO BALANCE CHANGES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/heroes/mccree/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;McCree&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Peacekeeper&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Alternate Fire&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recovery time (i.e. the amount of time before McCree starts reloading) decreased from 0.75 seconds to 0.3 seconds&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bullet damage decreased from 70 to 45&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments: &lt;/strong&gt;McCree was performing too well against all targets, making him feel like a must-pick in many situations. By reducing the damage of his alternate fire, McCree is now significantly weaker against tanks like Roadhog and Reinhardt, but still maintains his lethality against smaller targets like Tracer and Genji. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://playoverwatch.com/en-us/heroes/widowmaker/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Widowmaker&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Widows Kiss&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Alternate Fire (Scoped Shot)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Base damage decreased from 15 to 12 &lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Note: Scoped shot damage multiplier remains unchanged&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Headshot damage multiplier increased from 2x to 2.5x&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Players must now wait for the unscoping animation to completely finish before scoping&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;li&gt;Infra-Sight&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ultimate cost increased by 10%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Developer Comments: &lt;/strong&gt;In the right hands, Widowmaker can often feel unstoppableeven when just landing body shots instead of critical heads shots. The changes to her alternate fire weaken body shot damage while leaving her headshot damage unchanged. Additionally, we felt her Ultimate ability, Infra-Sight, was coming up a little too frequently, especially considering its impact on the game. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Improved stability of the High Bandwidth option in Custom Games&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Mercy to gain Ultimate charge whenever damage boosting an ally who was attacking a barrier or Ice Wall&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that allowed Reaper to Shadow Step to unintended locations on certain maps&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maps&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue with collision on certain areas of Dorado not blocking line of sight&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Recent Actions Against Cheating in Overwatch</title><description>We've recently taken action against Overwatch accounts worldwide which were found to be using cheat programs. Were committed to providing an equal and fair playing field for everyone in Overwatch, and will continue to take action against those found in violation of our Terms of Use. Cheating of any form will not be toleratedread more about our stance &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20743596231" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;If you believe another player is cheating or you have information pertaining to the use of hacks, bots, or unauthorized third-party software in Overwatch, please let us know! You can do so by using the right-click report functionality in the game, and/or by emailing &lt;strong&gt;hacks@blizzard.com&lt;/strong&gt;.</description></item><item><title>Overwatch Patch Notes - May 26, 2016</title><description>A new patch is now live on Windows PC. Read below to learn about the latest changes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813879/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;General Discussion &lt;/a&gt;forum.&lt;br/&gt;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813881/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;For troubleshooting assistance, visit our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/22813880/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Technical Support&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GENERAL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Added a new "ForceFMA" configuration option which can be set by users working with our support teams to mitigate a specific audio crash&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Cheating in Overwatch</title><description>Weve always taken cheating in Blizzard games very seriously, and that stance is no different for Overwatch. Play nice; play fair is one of our core values as a company, and its something weve taken to heart not only when designing the game, but also as weve developed our plans to support it and our players after launch. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;What does this mean for Overwatch? If a player is found to be cheatingor using hacks, bots, or third-party software that provides any sort of unfair advantagethat player will be permanently banned from the game. Full stop. Not only does cheating undermine the spirit of fair play that all of our products are based on, but it works to diminish the fun and enjoyment of others. While we are unlikely to publicly acknowledge when accounts are closed as a result of cheating or using unauthorized programs, we have and will continue to monitor Overwatch for exploitative behavior, as well as take action as needed to preserve the integrity of game. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;These assertions arent new or groundbreaking for Blizzard, but theyre important and serve as a reminder of our commitment to delivering epic gameplay experiences. For us, its not just about creating awesome games, but about supporting those games and their communities for years to come. The upcoming launch of Overwatch on May 24 is in many ways just the beginning, and were doing all that we can to prepare for that milestone and (perhaps more importantly) what comes afternot just in terms of new game content, but also how we can ensure a fair and equitable play environment for everyone.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;So, how can you help? &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to Report Cheating in Overwatch&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you believe another player is cheating or you have information pertaining to the use of hacks, bots, or unauthorized third-party software in Overwatch, please contact us at &lt;strong&gt;hacks@blizzard.com&lt;/strong&gt;. Although you wont receive a response, our dedicated team of engineers and analysts actively monitor this inbox for your reports. In fact, thanks to reports submitted during the beta, weve already made improvements to the game as well as removed players who were found to be cheating.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In addition, by popular request, we will also be including an option to report players for potential cheating directly through the game client. This option will be available at launch and can be accessed through the normal right click &gt; Report menu. &lt;br/&gt;	&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Things to Keep in Mind When Reporting Potential Cheating&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Encountering another player who you believe is cheating can be an incredibly frustrating experience, but in a game like Overwatch, we ask that you keep the following considerations in mind:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Our in-game camera system does not always play back footage at the same fidelity as real-time gameplay (this loss in fidelity applies to the killcam, Plays of the Game, Highlights, andto a lesser extentthe spectator camera as well). This can sometimes result in a players aim appearing more snappy or less fluid in playback than it did in-game.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;With the above, there may be bugs with the in-game camera system that affect playback footage. In the Closed Beta, we actually had a bug that caused the killcam and spectator camera angle to suddenly snap whenever Zarya cast Particle Barrier or Projected Barrier. While were unaware of any issues with the camera system at present, undiscovered bugs are always a possibility to consider. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lastly, some players are just really good at first-person shooters. Through practice and years of experience, these players movements and reaction times can occasionally appear unnatural (if not physically impossible) to those who may not have been exposed to that particular level of play before. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;It's important to note that while video evidence from killcams, Plays of the Game, Highlights, and other community captured footage can be very helpful, we will never use it alone to verify whether or not cheating is taking place. As a result, we encourage players to &lt;em&gt;play nice, play fair &lt;/em&gt;and avoid publicly accusing individuals of cheating whenever possible and instead use the reporting methods detailed above. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Thank you for your vigilance, passion, and commitment to helping us make Overwatch the best game it can be. We'll see you May 24!</description></item><item><title>REMINDER: Closed Beta Shutting Down April 25</title><description>As a friendly reminder, the Overwatch Closed Beta will be shutting down today at approximately 10:00 a.m. PDT (13:11 UTC). At that time, Closed Beta participants will no longer be able to log in to the beta client. Access to our Closed Beta forums will remain available until Friday, April 29, at which point they will also be shut down. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For more information, be sure to read our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/overwatch/en/blog/20098640/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt; official announcement&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In the meantime, we'd like to give a huge shoutout to everyone who's shared feedback about the game. Hero feedback, map feedback, UI feedback, matchmaking feedback, sound feedback, VFX feedback, performance feedback, forum feedback  we appreciate it all. Thank you for helping us make Overwatch as awesome as it can be. &amp;lt;3&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We'll see you in the &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/overwatch/en/blog/20100169/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Open Beta&lt;/a&gt;...and then on May 24 for launch!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;- The Overwatch Team</description></item><item><title> Overwatch Beta Patch Notes - April 21, 2016</title><description>A new beta patch is now live. Read below to learn about the latest changes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446649/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Feedback &lt;/a&gt;forum.&lt;br/&gt;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446651/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;MAP BALANCE CHANGES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hanamura&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The map has been put back into rotation. The issues affecting spawn room doors have been resolved&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HERO BALANCE CHANGES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;McCree&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Alternate fire recovery time (i.e. the time before McCree can shoot again) increased from 0.3 seconds to 0.75 seconds&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comments: McCrees alternate fire is intended to be more situational, but often players were using it as his primary way to deal damage. This change makes it weaker to use repeatedly, while maintaining its power as a finisher and as part of his roll combos.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zenyatta&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Harmony Orb&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Healing increased from 25 to 30 per second&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comments: Now that Zenyattas orbs are more restricted, we felt there was room to increase their healing output to help him in his support role.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue on Route 66 where the payload automatically advanced about 8 meters after the large doors opened without players of the attacking team being near it&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Overwatch Beta Patch Notes - April 19, 2016</title><description>A new beta patch is now live. Read below to learn about the latest changes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446649/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Feedback &lt;/a&gt;forum.&lt;br/&gt;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446651/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note that some changes may not be documented or described in full detail.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GENERAL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Progression Rewards&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Portrait Frames &lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gray portrait frame design removed (levels 1-100)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; All remaining portrait frame designs will now shift down one promotion as a result (i.e. players level 1-100 will now have a bronze frame, players level 100-200 will now have a bronze frame with a star, etc)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Removed some of the less popular sprays &lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Note: These sprays may return in future content patches&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;All heroes will have the same number of hero-specific sprays &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MAP BALANCE CHANGES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hanamura&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The map has been temporarily disabled to address an issue affecting spawn room doors&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Route 66&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Slowed the payload by 10%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Adjusted placement of the health packs across the map&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comments: We've noticed that attackers are winning more often than we'd like on Route 66, so we've made some adjustments to the payload speed and health pack placement to try to bring the attacker win rate more in line with our other escort maps. &lt;/em&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Volskaya Industries&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Moved initial spawn points to further back &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comments: We're also seeing attackers win more often than we'd like on Volskaya Industries, so we've pushed spawn points back a little bit in the library to help defenders hold objective A.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Statistics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed issue where shooting a barrier counted as a miss for Widowmakers Scoped Accuracy statistic &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed issue where shooting a turret or barrier counted as a miss for Pharahs Rocket Direct Hits statistic&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Soldier: 76s Final Blows average statistic in the end of round scoreboard is now correct&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weekly Brawl&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed several interactions with barriers in the Arcade Weekly Brawl&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Scheduled Beta Maintenance - April 16, 2015</title><description>Following the conclusion of our final Beta Test Weekend today at 9:00 PM PDT, we will be bringing down the Overwatch beta for scheduled maintenance. We expect this maintenance to be relatively short and for the beta to be available again at approximately 10:00 PM PDT.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note that during this maintenance, all Beta Test Weekend participants will have their beta access removed. At that point, these players will no longer be able to log in to the game or post in our beta forums.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Players with Closed Beta access will be otherwise unaffected and able to continue playing (and posting) as normal after maintenance concludes.</description></item><item><title>Overwatch Beta Patch Notes - April 15, 2016</title><description>A new beta patch is now live. Read below to learn about the latest changes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446649/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Feedback &lt;/a&gt;forum.&lt;br/&gt;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446651/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Players will no longer be prompted to play through Training modes each time they log in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused the in-game tutorial to not advance &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a few issues with the in-game matchmaker that were causing games not to populate or matches to complete&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Improved handling for players using Widows 7&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title> Overwatch Beta Patch Notes - April 13, 2016</title><description>A new beta patch is now live. Read below to learn about the latest changes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446649/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Feedback &lt;/a&gt;forum.&lt;br/&gt;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446651/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note that some changes may not be documented or described in full detail.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GENERAL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competitive Play&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Players in Heroic can now be matched into a Competitive Play game with non-Heroic players, but only after waiting in queue for a moderate period of time&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Progression Rewards&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Added "Nomad" Genji Legendary skin&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Added "Raindancer" Pharah Legendary skin&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Performance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Implemented several CPU efficiency improvements for CPUs that do not support hyper-threading&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MAP BALANCE CHANGES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Volskaya Industries&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Increased time required to capture both objectives &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;King's Row&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Increased time required to capture the first objective &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HERO BALANCE CHANGES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;McCree &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Flashbang &lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stun duration increased by 0.2 seconds&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recovery time (i.e. the time before McCree can shoot again) increased by 0.2 seconds&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer Comments: This change should help McCree better orient to his targets after stunning them with Flashbang, and give his teammates more opportunities to capitalize on its use.  &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reinhardt&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Earthshatter &lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reinhardt no longer gains Ultimate charge from using Earthshatter&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: This is general rule we have in place that prevents heroes from generating Ultimate charge when using their Ultimate, but Reinhardt was previously overlooked. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Roadhog&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Chain Hook&lt;/li&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Now pulls smaller targets closer than larger targets&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Whole Hog&lt;/li&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Decreased the movement speed penalty&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: The change to Chain Hook should enable Roadhog to more reliably kill smaller heroes after a successful pull. Since Roadhogs primary fire has such a wide spread, this allowed smaller heroes to avoid the majority of incoming damage from Roadhog after they were hooked.  For Whole Hog, we feel the movement change helps the ability be more flexible while also making it less dangerous for Roadhog to use.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused respawning players to face in the direction of the Kill Cam feed&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that sometimes caused players to respawn twice &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that prevented players from being able to cancel out of matchmaking once queued&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue with Competitive Play that would cause the game to start before all slots on both teams were filled &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where the End of Match would only show the Victory Lineup&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue with the sizing of sprays on specific surfaces in Route 66&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User Interface&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where Custom Reticle could not be reset to default&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Fixed an issue where Custom Reticle was not persisting&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused chat to scroll &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where hero-specific bindings would reset after round transition on a Control map&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed where selecting ALT + Z on the Highlights menu would display a black screen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Scheduled Beta Maintenance - April 12, 2016</title><description>We will be performing scheduled maintenance beginning today, April 12, at 2:00 PM PDT and expect the service to be available again at approximately 4:00 p.m. PDT. During this time, the Overwatch beta will be unavailable in all gameplay regions.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please follow &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/BlizzardCS" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;@BlizzardCS&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/BlizzardCSEU_EN" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;BlizzardCSEU_EN&lt;/a&gt; on Twitter for further updates.</description></item><item><title> Overwatch Beta Patch Notes - April 6, 2016</title><description>A new beta patch is now live. Read below to learn about the latest changes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446649/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Feedback &lt;/a&gt;forum.&lt;br/&gt;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446651/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note that some changes may not be documented or described in full detail.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GENERAL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Soldier: 76 has been re-enabled for all game modes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Added some transparency to Widowmakers scope graphic when scoped in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Added  Young Genji Legendary skin&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Several new sprays have been added for Bastion, Mei, Mercy, Pharah, and Winston&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused the killcam and spectator camera angle to suddenly snap whenever Zarya cast Particle Barrier or Projected Barrier&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mercys damage beam will now correctly amplify its targets damage&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where Widowmakers scope graphic wasnt rendering when scoped in &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maps&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a collision issue with the theater door outside the attacking spawn in Hollywood&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skins&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue with the implementation of Commando: 76 and Night Ops: 76 Legendary skins &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused Scarecrow Junkats Steel Trap to be unkillable&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue with hero weapons not appearing for several skins &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Overwatch Beta Patch Notes - April 5, 2016</title><description>A new beta patch is now live. Read below to learn about the latest changes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446649/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Feedback &lt;/a&gt;forum.&lt;br/&gt;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446651/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note that some changes may not be documented or described in full detail.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PATCH HIGHLIGHTS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Play Mode: Competitive Play&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Earned some battlefield experience and ready to step up your game? Prepare to prove yourself in Competitive Play! Designed for those seeking a more serious challenge, Competitive Play is our new game mode in which players can compete and rank up through a series divisions and tiers in monthly seasons.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To join a Competitive Play game, select Play from the main menu and then select Competitive Play. You can queue up for Competitive Play games solo or in a group (of any size). Once queued, the system will do its best to match you against other players who've also queued solo or, if you're playing with friends, against players who queued in similarly-sized groups. Please note that you must be at least level 25 in order queue for Competitive Play. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Competitive Play is still a work in progress and will, like all beta content, be subject to before the game releaseslikely based on your feedback! To learn more about Competitive Play, &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/overwatch/en/blog/20090466/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GENERAL:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Progression Rewards&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Several new sprays, player icons, and voice lines have been added&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Some of the less popular sprays and voice lines have been removed&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;New Legendary skins have been added for several heroes: &lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gearbot Bastion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Junebug D.Va&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Scavenger D.Va&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sparrow Genji&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fool Junkrat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hayseed Junkrat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Scarecrow Junkrat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Breakaway Lcio&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Slapshot Lcio&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Abominable Mei&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Yeti Hunter Mei&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Raptorion Pharah&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Thunderbird Pharah&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Plague Doctor Reaper&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stonehardt Reinhardt&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Islander Roadhog&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sharkbait Roadhog&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Commando: 76 Solider:76&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Night Ops: 76 Soldier: 76&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Comtesse Widowmaker&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Huntress Widowmaker&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Arctic Zarya&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Siberian Front Zarya&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Leaving Games&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leaver Penalty&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;If a players game completion percentage falls below our required threshold, they will now receive a warning message (this percentage is calculated based on their 20 most recent games)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If that players continues to leave games after receiving this warning, they will incur a 75% XP penalty for future games&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This penalty will be removed once the player raises their game completion percentage above our required threshold (again, this percentage is calculated based on their 20 most recent games) &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Play Interactivity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Players who are in the team spawn room and have selected a hero will no longer be removed for inactivity until 45 seconds after a game has started&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Players actively browsing heroes in the Assemble Heroes selection screen will no longer be considered inactive &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Removed initial warning message displayed after leaving a game&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Note: Competitive Play will have additional rules and penalties for leaving games&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technical Updates&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Network Graph&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You can now enable a network graph while in-game to help diagnose client networking issues&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hit CTRL+SHIFT+N to toggle the network graph on or off&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Network Quality Status Icons&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The client will now pulse network status icons when packet loss or a network stream stall is detected&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You can disable these icons from the Gameplay settings menu&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;High Bandwidth Custom Game Option&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You can now enable a high bandwidth mode for Custom Game, changing the client update rate from 20.8Hz to 62.5Hz&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Improved the regularity of player commands being sent from the client to the sever&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reduced the maximum rewind time allowed on behalf of high-latency players&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Note: High-latency players will now extrapolate and potentially mispredict as a result &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MAP BALANCE CHANGES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Control Maps&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Each round now has a unique name  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rounds are now shuffled in random order&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ilios&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minor revisions to art and collision have been made throughout the map&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lijiang Tower&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The control point room in the Garden has been enlarged&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The pillars in the Control Center have been removed and two new walls have been added&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Route 66&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Revised first tunnel on the left outside of the starting attacker spawn&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Removed ability for players to enter the hanging train above the starting attacker spawn&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Further adjusted payload size to ensure all heroes can move around it in narrow locations &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Significant revisions to collision have been made throughout the map&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HERO BALANCE CHANGES: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mei&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ice Wall&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Can now be destroyed early by activating the ability again&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: This is a simple quality-of-life change that helps Mei have better control of her Ice Wall.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mercy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Caduceus Blaster&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Now automatically reloads when not in use&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;li&gt;Caduceus Staff&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Players can now swap between healing beam and damage beam without losing the beams target&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;li&gt;Guardian Angel&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Range increased slightly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cooldown decreased from 2 seconds to 1.5 seconds &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Will now destroy environmental objects when you come in contact with them &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Can now be cancelled by using the ability again&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: Some quality-of-life improvements for Mercy players, as well as overall improvements to Guardian Angel. We think the changes will help her reliability and survivability when she is the middle of a firefight.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Symmetra&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Photon Shield&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Shield amount reduced from 50 to 25&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: We feel that Symmetra's win rate is still too high at all levels of play. We want to do a pretty big swing here to see how it impacts her overall. This is a significant change that we'll be monitoring closely.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Torbjrn&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rivet Gun&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Now automatically reloads when not in use &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: Similar to the pistol change for Mercy, this is a simple quality-of-life change that helps streamline using multiple weapons.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;USER INTERFACE: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Career Overview&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reorganized the statistics on the Main Overview, Hero Comparison, and Hero Statistics pages &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Averages shown are now per game averages, updated from per minute &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Game Options&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;An option to select custom crosshairs has been added &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The following hero-specific options are now available:&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Genji&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Automatically climb walls&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hanzo&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Automatically climb walls&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Junkrat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;RIP-Tire: Automatically climb walls&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mercy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Toggle Beam Connection&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reinhardt&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Toggle Barrier&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Soldier: 76&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hold to Sprint&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Widowmaker&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Toggle Zoom&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mouse Sensitivity While Zoomed&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mouse sensitivity scale has been reset and re-calibrated &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spectating&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Several polish updates have been made to Spectator Mode&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BUG FIXES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maps&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue on Watchpoint: Gibraltar that allowed players to access out of map areas &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where leaver penalties were being incorrectly applied to an account &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Overwatch Beta Patch Notes - March 30, 2016</title><description>A new beta patch is now live. Read below to learn about the latest changes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446649/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Feedback &lt;/a&gt;forum.&lt;br/&gt;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446651/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note that some changes may not be documented or described in full detail.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GENERAL:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Matchmaking&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; Several behind-the-scenes improvements have been made to the in-game matchmaker.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BUG FIXES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; should now save and carry over between sessions (for reals this time)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a several crashes that could occur when viewing Highlights&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reinhardts Charge should now pin enemy targets more reliably&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Zarya will no longer gain power if Projected Barrier is cast on an ally that is also shielded by Lcios Sound Barrier&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an exploit that allowed players to become invulnerable if Zarya casted Projected Barrier on them and then immediately switched heroes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Overwatch Beta Patch Notes - March 25, 2016</title><description>A new beta patch is now live. Read below to learn about the latest changes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446649/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Feedback&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446651/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note that some changes may not be documented or described in full detail.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BUG FIXES: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The AFK timer will now only start after a player has selected a hero &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where using the Enter key in a Custom Game lobby would open Custom Game settings&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maps&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a few issues with payload collision on Route 66&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that prevented D.Va from being able to launch her mech while activating Self-Destruct&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue with some skins that caused elements to be missing during Widowmakers Infra-Sight&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sound&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Voice Chat is no longer Off by default&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;End-of-round commendations should now play the proper sounds and VO whenever a player receives five or more votes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zenyattas Orb of Harmony now plays the active healing sound effect&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spectating&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Player levels should now appear in Spectator Mode&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User Interface&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where the Social Menu would become a black screen between rounds&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where allied health bars would appear as red&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where health bars would not show after damage to an enemy was dealt&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where the On Fire effect was not displaying on the Scoreboard&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Overwatch Beta Patch Notes - March 22, 2016</title><description>A new beta patch is now live. Read below to learn about the latest changes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446649/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Feedback &lt;/a&gt;forum.&lt;br/&gt;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446651/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note that some changes may not be documented or described in full detail.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PATCH HIGHLIGHTS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Escort Map: Route 66&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Though the travelers and road trippers who used to cross the US on historic Route 66 are gone, the Main Street of America still stands, a testament to a simpler time. The gas stations, roadside shops, and cafes have gone into disuse, and the fabled Deadlock Gorge is mostly seen from the comfort of transcontinental train cars. But amid the fading monuments of that earlier era, the outlaws of the Deadlock Gang are planning their biggest heist yet.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Play Mode: Weekly Brawl!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Similar to its namesake feature in Hearthstone, Weekly Brawls are a fun, alternative way to play Overwatch. Each week, well rotate in a different Weekly Brawl featuring a set of unique (and sometimes crazy) rules from our Custom Game system. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For example: In one Weekly Brawl, youll only be able to play Soldier: 76, while in another Weekly Brawl, a random hero will be selected for you each time you respawn. Other Weekly Brawls will restrict you to Support heroes only, or Tank heroes only, or Defense heroes onlyand more! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To join a Weekly Brawl, select "Play" from the main menu and then select "Weekly Brawl!" You can queue up solo or in a party, and youll be matched into a 6v6 game versus other players. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; NOTE: For the purposes of testing, Weekly Brawls are currently set to rotate once per day rather than once per week. This cadence is for the beta only and will be return to its normally-scheduled weekly rotation in the near future. &amp;lt;&amp;lt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: We love the Tavern Brawl system in Hearthstone and are excited to bring a similar style of play into Overwatch. However, even though we think Weekly Brawls can add a lot of fun to the game, the feature is still a work in progress and something we consider more of an experiment for now. In the meantime, we hope you enjoy testing the sample Weekly Brawls weve set up and look forward to your feedback! &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Feature: Highlights&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To complement our Play of the Game feature, personal gameplay highlights may now be surfaced to players via the main menu after theyve completed at least one match. The game can currently store up to five of the most recent highlights from your active gaming session.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note that there is currently no way to export your highlights from the game client and that all highlights will be reset whenever you log out.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Updated Feature: Play of the Game&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Overall, the Play of the Game feature has been a lot of fun and well-received by the community. However, there are still a lot of improvements wed like to make so that the gameplay highlighted at the end of each match is more varied and interesting to watch. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To that end, we will now be capturing different types of gameplay during a matchbased on four new categoriesand then comparing those moments against each other to find the best Play of the Game for that round of play. The new Play of the Game categories available in this patch are as follows:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;High Score:&lt;/strong&gt; This category is intended to feature large multikills and quick killstreaks. The larger the multikill, the quicker the kill streak, and the closer one is to an objective will all increase a players High Score score. (Note: This is the category under which all existing Plays of the Game would fall.)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lifesaver: &lt;/strong&gt;This category is intended to feature situations where one player is able to save another player (or players) from imminent death. For example: If a Reinhardt has an enemy pinned, and that enemys teammate stuns or kills the Reinhardt, the teammate would be awarded a large amount of Lifesaver score. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sharpshooter: &lt;/strong&gt;This category is intended to feature difficult or skillful kills. For this category, the game will be looking at factors like movement speed, the distance at which the attack occurred, whether or not the attack was a headshot, and if the victim of the attack was in the air at the time, etc. Each of these variables will increase a players Sharpshooter score.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shutdown:&lt;/strong&gt; This category is intended to feature moments in which one player kills another player (or players) right as they were about to do something particularly impactful. An example of this would be if a Widowmaker snipes a Lcio in the middle casting Sound Barrier for his team. In this instance, the game will predict how impactful that Sound Barrier would have been and then award the Widowmaker player an appropriate Shutdown score in return. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The player who has the highest score in any one of these four categories at the end of the match will receive the Play of the Game. If the winning Play of the Game category is Lifesaver, Sharpshooter, or Shutdown then the category name will be called out during the highlight intro. If the winning category is High Score, however, no callout will be provided. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;With these additions, weve also retuned some of the existing Play of the Game ratings to make it more viable for other abilities gain the spotlightlike Mercys Resurrect. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: This is just the start of what we want to achieve with Plays of the Game, but we wanted to get these initial changes into your hands as soon as possible so you can work with us to make the system even better. In the future, well be looking to add new features to the Play of the Game system, toosuch as dynamic cameras for playback, as well as more varied categories. So get out there and play and let us know what you think!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GENERAL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Player Progression&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Achievements have been added&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;All available and unlocked achievements can be viewed in the Career Profile &gt; Achievements tab&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Select achievements will now unlock general and hero-specific sprays (which can be equipped in the Hero Gallery)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Players will now unlock a new portrait frame every 10 levels, instead of only at levels 10, 25, 50, and 100&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Promotions have been added&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Players will now receive a promotion every 100 levels&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;When a player receives a promotion, they will unlock a new portrait frame theme&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;With each new promotion, the players level (and the EXP required to level) will be reset&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;New Legendary skins have been added for several heroes:&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;"Antique" Bastion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Junker D.Va&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stinger D.Va&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Jester Junkrat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;"Hip Hopper" Lcio&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;"Riverboat" McCree&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;"Vigilante" McCree&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Nevermore Reaper&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;"Stunt Rider: 76" Soldier: 76"&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Barbarossa Torbjrn&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Blackbeard Torbjrn&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;"Cybergoth" Zarya&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Plays of the Games have received a polish pass (see above)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Joining and Leaving Games&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Consecutive Match Bonus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Players will now receive an EXP bonus for playing multiple matches in succession&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Player Backfill Match Bonus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Players who backfill into a match will no longer receive a loss for that match (even if it ends in a defeat), but can still receive a win&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;These players will also receive an additional EXP bonus for the match, if completed&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leaver Penalty&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Players who leave an in-progress match will now receive an automatic loss&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Players who repeatedly leave in-progress matches will also receive a temporary penalty on EXP gained from future matches (this penalty will persist as long as the player continues to repeatedly leave in-progress matches) &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: The consecutive match bonus, along with the leaver penalty, should hopefully incentivize players to complete the matches they begin. Unfortunately, many players have been leaving in-game matches at the first sign of difficulty, even in games where their team could still win. As a result, the leaving players team would be at a large disadvantage until a backfill could be found. Speaking of backfills: We want the process of joining an in-progress match to be a positive experience, even if you happen to enter right as the game ends. To assist with this, players who backfill matches will still receive a notable amount of experience, regardless of how long they played. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Group Improvements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Players can now request to Join a Group&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;When a group leader leaves a game, he or she will now have the option to leave with the group intact&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expanded preferences for groups have been added to the Options menu:&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Option to allow current group members to invite other players to the group&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Option to allow Anyone, Friends, or No One to join your group without an invite&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Miscellaneous&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The new player experience has been updated&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Tutorial and Practice Range have received a polish pass&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dialogs will now guide new players through the Tutorial, Practice Range, and Practice vs AI modes before recommending Quick Play&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Players can now browse the main menu while queued for Quick Play, Play vs AI, or Weekly Brawl! games&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Healing Done has replaced Final Blows as an available end-of-match medal&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;End-of-match commendations have received another tuning pass&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;AI heroes will now melee and use Health Packs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MAP BALANCE CHANGES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nepal&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;New routes have been added for the first and second control points&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Removed some walls around the second control point&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HERO BALANCE CHANGES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The following hero abilities will now ignore payloads during Line of Sight checks:&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lcio &gt; Crossfade and Sound Barrier&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mei &gt; Blizzard&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reinhardt &gt; Earthshatter&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Soldier: 76 &gt; Biotic Field&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zenyatta &gt; Transcendence&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: Were relaxing the line of sight restrictions payloads can cause for certain abilities, where it makes sense. This change should hopefully make these abilities feel more consistent when playing on Escort maps. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zenyatta&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Orb of Harmony and Orb of Discord&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Now automatically return if their targets are out of line of sight for more than 3 seconds&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: We realize this is a pretty major change, but its one wed like to test and see how it plays out. The fire and forget playstyle that many Zenyatta players utilize for orb placement not only has caused several balance issues, but also made the hero a lot less interesting to play. With this change, instead of putting Orb of Harmony on a single person and leaving it on them until they die, Zenyatta players will now need to move the orb around more frequently to effectively heal their team. This change also allows for enemies to be able to shake off an Orb of Discord if they disengage for some time.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;USER INTERFACE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Options Menu&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gameplay&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Players can now choose to skip Skirmish Mode while in queue&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Control&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Players can now save/set hero-specific keybindings&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sound&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Support for Dolby ATMOS Headphones has been added&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;For optimal performance, use regular headphones and change the default playback device to stereo.  For USB headphones that emulate 5.1 or 7.1, you may need to turn off any surround emulation in the headphones drivers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Any recording or streaming done with ATMOS Headphones setting enabled will contain the same ATMOS encoded mix.  The viewing audience should also be using headphones for optimal viewing.  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Switching the ATMOS mode while music is playing will kill the music that is playing until new music is retriggered.  This is a known issue and we are investigating a fix.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In-Game UI&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The payload progress bar now shows checkpoints as well as the distance to upcoming checkpoints (if &amp;lt; 5m)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Capture point UI art has been updated&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Social Menu&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;All social menu screens have been updated with new art&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A Recent Players list is now available&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The ability to Rate Players has been moved to the social menu (from the end-of-match screen)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;This means that players can rate their teammates at any time via the social menu, rather just at the end of a match&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Note: Rate this Match can still only be accessed via the end-of-match screen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Players can now report other players through the social menu&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keybindings should now always save and carry over between sessions correctly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Players with full health, but less than full shields will now appear to have taken damage to healers (when looking at their hero outlines)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;It is no longer possible for some AoE weapons to deal damage to an enemy player if that player is on the other side of wall theyre partially clipping into&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ultimate charge should no longer reset whenever a player selects a different hero and then cancels while dead&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lcios Crossfade buff should now properly reapply to all allies after a round transition on Control maps&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Meis Cryostasis and Ice Wall should now always display the appropriate team colors&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Symmetras Sentry Turrets should no longer acquire targets from inside Meis Ice Wall&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Scoped shots against enemy turrets should no longer count as misses when calculating Widowmakers Scoped Accuracy statistic&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed several issues where the slow effect applied by Meis Endothermic Blast and Blizzard were being reset&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where Reinhardts Charge would sometimes knock back a target that should have been pinned&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where Symmetra Sentry Turrets couldnt be placed in select (but otherwise intended) areas &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where some damage sources prevented by Zaryas Particle Barrier werent increasing her Ultimate charge&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User Interface&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Left Mouse Button and Right Mouse Button icons should now render in the F1 help menus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;UI notifications for objectives should no longer persist on screen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Overwatch Beta Patch Notes - March 17, 2016</title><description>A new beta patch is now live. Read below to learn about the latest changes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446649/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Feedback &lt;/a&gt;forum.&lt;br/&gt;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446651/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note that some changes may not be documented or described in full detail.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HERO BALANCE CHANGES: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Quick Melee&lt;/li&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Damage decreased from 50 to 30 &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cooldown decreased from 1.5 seconds to 1 second&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: Quick Melee has proven to be too strong of an ability, especially when used in combination with other attacks to increase burst damage potential. Lowering the damage of a melee attack also allows us to lower the cooldown, making it feel more responsive when you need it.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bastion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tank Mode &lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Duration reduced from 10 seconds to 8 seconds&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: We like the way Bastions ultimate is performing, but it is lasting just a bit too long for enemies to reasonably react to it. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Genji&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Health increased from 150 to 200&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Shuriken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Damage reduced by 20%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: Weve been listening to feedback and watching data very closely on Genji, especially since we recently lowered his health. Overall that change did put him in a better place, but we want to try an alternative change by lowering his damage output instead of his survivability.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hanzo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Scatter Arrow &lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fragments will no longer be calculated as a headshot against an enemy player&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: We wanted to reduce some of the more frustrating elements of Scatter Arrow while still maintaining its overall power level. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Junkrat&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;RIP-Tire&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; Health reduced from 150 to 100&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: The recent changes to Junkrats RIP-Tire have helped it become more viable and have opened up new options for enemy counters. However, the health was too high, so many times it felt impossible to counter.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mei&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Endothermic Blaster &lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Primary Fire&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lowered time to freeze by 15%&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Secondary Fire &lt;/li&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Added damage falloff &lt;li&gt;Lowered fire rate by 15%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: Since last patch we have seen Mei perform significantly better across the board. Even though her overall power level is in a much better place now, too much of that power is coming from her alternate fire. This change moves some of that power from her alternate fire to her primary fire.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Symmetra&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Teleporter&lt;/li&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ultimate charge cost increased by 30%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: Teleport was coming up so frequently that it didnt feel rewarding to eliminate Symmetras Teleport Pad. This change should help reward those who hunt down the Teleport Pad while encouraging Symmetra players to find more strategic locations for deployment. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winston&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Jump Pack&lt;/li&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cooldown reduced from 8 seconds to 6 seconds&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: Winstons survivability took a hit when we recently made changes to Barrier Projector. Overall, Winston being less reliant on a single ability has been good, but were looking at bumping his power back up in other ways. Lowering the Jump Pack cooldown allows him to use the ability as a normal engage tool while also giving him more flexibility to use it as an escape option or to continue pressuring the enemy. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zarya&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Particle Cannon&lt;/li&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Increased the minimum damage by 25%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: Zaryas main strength comes from her ability to absorb damage to increase her own power. While we dont want to undermine that core functionality, we also want to make sure she feels as though she provides a meaningful contribution in combat even at lower power levels. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zenyatta&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Discord Orb &lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Now removed by Immunity Effects (Mei Cryo-Freeze, Zarya Barriers, Zenyatta Transcendence)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments:  Discord Orb is a powerful tool that has proven a little too difficult to deal with at times. Were allowing for some more options to counter the ability while still maintaining its strength. &lt;/em&gt;</description></item><item><title>Possible Interruptions - March 11, 2016</title><description>As part of our ongoing efforts to prepare Overwatch for its May 24 launch, we'll be performing a variety of tests on our hardware over the next 4-6 hours. During this time, players may experience interruptions of service including disconnects. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We anticipate this performance testing to conclude sometime after 4pm PST. In the meantime, thank you for helping us make Overwatch an awesome game, and apologies in advance for any inconvenience!</description></item><item><title>Overwatch Beta Patch Notes - March 10, 2016</title><description>A new beta patch is now live. Read below to learn about the latest changes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446649/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Feedback&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446651/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note that some changes may not be documented or described in full detail.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BUG FIXES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Custom Game host permissions should now correctly transfer to another player whenever the original host leaves&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused the "Most Environmental Kills" commendation to display "Lifetime Environment Kills" as the primary statistic&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maps&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ilios&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Updated several in-game locations and objects to prevent players from being able to reach, stand, and/or get stuck on them&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where a large health pack was missing near the third Control point &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Overwatch Beta Patch Notes - March 8, 2016</title><description>A new beta patch is now live. Read below to learn about the latest changes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446649/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Feedback&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446651/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note that some changes may not be documented or described in full detail.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PATCH HIGHLIGHTS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Control Map: Ilios&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Situated atop a small island rising from the Aegean Sea, Ilios is a postcard-perfect Mediterranean town, with a bustling harborside, winding paths for rambling hillside strolls, and gorgeous vistas. It is the ideal vacation stop for people looking for a place to relax, or for those interested in exploring the ruins scattered at the top of the island, where many artifacts and relics of the ancient world have been recently unearthed.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Career Profile Reset&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This patch includes a full wipe of players Career Profiles. As a result, the Career Profile page will appear empty when you first log in after patching, and your previous "Personal Best" records will be reset.  (Note: This wipe will not affect matchmaking, player levels, progression, or rewards.)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GENERAL:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Map Updates&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Health pack placement has been adjusted across all maps&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Payload sizes have been adjusted to ensure that all heroes can move around them in narrow locations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Numbani&lt;/li&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Significant art changes have been made throughout the map&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; Temple of Anubis &lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A new route has been added to reach the second capture point&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The temple gate leading to the second capture point is now wider&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Play Modes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Play vs. A.I.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Players can now select their desired A.I. difficulty (Easy, Medium, Hard)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Added kill cam functionality&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Added Zarya and Roadhog as A.I. opponents &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Custom Game&lt;/li&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Added the ability to invite players by using their BattleTag &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Added the ability to auto-fill teams with invited players or A.I.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Added Zarya and Roadhog as A.I. opponents&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Progression Rewards&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Several new sprays have been added &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Signature, cheer, and taunt emote rewards are now available for all heroes &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;New Legendary skins and themes have been added for several heroes:&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Steambot Bastion &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;"Wooden Bastion &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Space Frog Lcio &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mystery Man McCree &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Raptorion Pharah&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Lionhardt Reinhardt&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spirit of: 76 Soldier: 76&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Miscellaneous&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Default emotes have been added for all heroes and are immediately available in the communications wheel&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;End-of-match commendations have received a tuning pass&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;End-of-match medal art has been updated&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mercy has been recast for the English version of the game&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; &lt;em&gt;Developer comments: When casting for Overwatch, we often try to find actors who are fluent in the characters native language. In the case of Mercy, we were able to find an actress that both captured the essence of the character and was able to speak German, which you will be able to hear in this version.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HERO BALANCE CHANGES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Junkrat&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;RIP-Tire&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ultimate charge cost increased by 25%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: After last patchs improvements to RIP-Tire, the speed at which Junkrat could activate his Ultimate was too frequent in comparison. Since RIP-Tire now has a much higher impact, weve adjusted the cost of his Ultimate to reflect that.  &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lcio&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Health increased from 150 to 200&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Sonic Amplifier &lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Damage reduced by 20%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt; Projectile size slightly reduced&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt; Sound Barrier &lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ultimate charge cost increased by 25%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: Weve been listening to feedback from all sources and decided to try some alternate changes to Lcio, taking a different approach from the last patch. The goal here is to let Lcio to be a difficult support to kill, but reduce his combat effectiveness and make him less of a good duelist. We also felt Lcio could also activate his Sound Barrier too frequently considering its impact, so the cost of his Ultimate has been adjusted as a result. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mei&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Endothermic Blaster &lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Alternative Fire Projectile speed increased by 50%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fire rate increased by 25% &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ammunition cost reduced from 40 to 25&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: In an ideal world, Mei is selected for her control and resilience, rather than her damage output. That said, we felt that there was still room to give her more consistent damage without compromising these goals. These changes are pretty significant, so well be watching their impact closely.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zenyatta&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Orb of Harmony and Orb of Discord will no longer stack with each other&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Transcendence&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Ultimate charge cost increased by 25%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: Zenyattas orb stacking could cause some degenerate situationssuch as a player becoming nearly un-killable if he or she had several Orbs of Harmony buffs active at the same time. Also, much like Lcio, we felt like Zenyatta could activate Transcendence too frequently considering its impact on a game, so his Ultimate cost has been scaled up to accommodate. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BUG FIXES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spectating&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The On Fire mechanic while viewed through the Spectator Mode UI should scale down appropriately with the size of hero portraits &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Developer Update | Popular Community Topics #2</title><description>If you havent gotten the chance to watch our latest Developer Update with game director Jeff Kaplan, make sure to check it out &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4pLuXWNDsp4" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In this video, Jeff covers some of the inherent challenges the team has experienced when trying to develop a Ranked Play mode, as well as how these complexities impact and relate to matchmaking. Jeff also takes a moment to discuss how we've approached the Closed Beta, revealing lessons that he's learned and sharing an apology to those who are eager to but cannot yet play the game. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We really enjoy being able to share these with everyone so thank you for your continued support and interest.</description></item><item><title>Overwatch Beta Patch Notes - March 1, 2016</title><description>A new beta patch is now live. Read below to learn about the latest changes.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446649/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Feedback&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446651/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note that some changes may not be documented or described in full detail.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GENERAL:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gameplay&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The speed at which a payload moves has been increased for when one player is escorting and when two players are escorting &lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Max speed (when 3+ players are escorting) remains unchanged &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Loot Boxes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;All sprays and voice lines are now considered Common&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;All player icons and victory poses are now considered Rare (excluding default icons and poses)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rare and Epic quantities of credits will now appear more frequently in Loot Boxes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Legendary quantities of credits will now appear less frequently in Loot Boxes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Matchmaking&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Several behind-the-scenes improvements have been made to the in-game matchmaker, especially for groups and players at higher skill levels&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Players from Australia, South America, and Southeast Asia should no longer experience exceptionally long queue times&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Social Wheel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Removed the cooldown when using voice lines&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Added a short global cooldown when using any option in the communications wheel&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Frequently spamming any option in the communications wheel within a short period of time will now lock you out for a few seconds (HI THERE!)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HERO BALANCE CHANGES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Were experimenting with some pretty significant balance changes this patch. Because this is beta, these changes are a little more aggressive than what you can expect to see once the game is livebut its the perfect environment for us try things out. Please continue to share your feedback with us and remember that everything in the Closed Beta is still subject to change!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bastion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Aim restrictions have been removed when transforming&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Configuration: Sentry&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Damaging Bastions core when in Sentry Mode will now cause double damage, decreased from triple damage&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: With the changes we made to Bastions overall survivability in Sentry Mode in our last beta patch, we felt that its core no longer needed to be so vulnerable. We also wanted to continue supporting Bastions run-and-gun playstyle, so we removed all aiming restrictions when transforming. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Genji&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Health decreased from 200 to 150&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: Genji is a fast character with a smaller character model, making him overly difficult to kill. To help address this, were lowering Genjis health. This is just an experiment, and we want to see how he feels to play (and play against) after this change. Be sure to share your feedback!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lcio&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Health decreased from 200 to 150&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: Similar to Genji, Lcio is fast, small, and has a lot of mobility options. Weve lowered his health slightly to compensate. Let us know how this feels!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Junkrat&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;RIP-Tire&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Health increased to 150&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If the tire is destroyed, it no longer detonates &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Significantly decreased damage falloff within RIP-Tires detonation radius&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: Junkrat is able to dish out a ton of damage, but RIP-Tire in its current state feels a little weak. On the flip side, trying to destroy his RIP-Tire can sometimes feel a little hopeless once it gets too close to you. With these changes, we hope that players will feel more empowered to take out Junkrats RIP-Tire before it explodes; however, to compensate, the explosion itself is much stronger. Overall, using RIP-Tire should feel more effective, and countering RIP-Tire should feel more realistic. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mei&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Endothermic Blaster&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Primary Fire&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Now has a minimum slow effect thats applied instantly&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The total time to freeze a target remains unchanged&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Blizzard &lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Effective radius can no longer be blocked by barriers or payloads &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: Mei is intended to be a good pick against the faster, more agile heroes in the game. However, the way her primary fire previously worked, thered frequently be situations where shed hit an enemy target briefly, but not long enough to slow them down or follow-up with another attack before they were out of range or line-of-sight. Boosting her primary fires initial slow effect should help her keep up with her enemy targets more successfully. Additionally, Meis Ultimate now ignores barriers like Winstons Barrier Projector and Reinhardts Barrier Field, which gives it a little more power and allows for more options when trying to counter heavy use of shielding abilities in general.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mercy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Guardian Angel&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Can once again target the souls of dead allies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: Players really enjoyed being able to use Guardian Angel on dead allies, and felt it allowed for more clutch plays and interesting movement options during combat. As a result, were reverting the change from a previous patch that removed Mercys ability to target and travel to dead allies using Guardian Angel. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Winston&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Barrier Projection&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Shield health decreased from 1000 to 600&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cooldown now activates after the barrier expires&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: Even though its always been possible to destroy Winstons Barrier Projection, it often felt impossible to do so in a normal situation unless you used your Ultimate. This resulted in many players just waiting for the barrier to expire instead of attacking it. With this change, its now more realistic for players to counter Winstons barrier through normal damage. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zarya&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Projected Barrier&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Duration decreased from 4 seconds to 2 seconds &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: Previously, Zaryas Projected Barrier lasted much longer than her Particle Barrier, which made it very difficult for enemies to deal with. If a player wanted to avoid dealing damage to the barrier, they had to wait a full 4 secondswhich felt like an unreasonable amount of time in the thick of combat. This change makes Zaryas Particle Barrier and Projected Barrier the same duration. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zenyatta&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Players will now receive a notification whenever Orb of Harmony or Orb of Destruction are returned from a dead target&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: This was a player suggestion that made a lot of sense to us. The notification helps you be more aware of the status of active Orbs of Harmony and Discordwhich, in turn, allows you to more strategically re-deploy them. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BUG FIXES: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a crash that could occur when getting a Play of the Game on a Control point&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed several crashes that could occur when logging into and out of the game client&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue with the way Torbjrns turret oriented whenever its target moved out of line-of-sight&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Loot Boxes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue with the lighting on several Loot Box rewards that caused skins and poses to appear darker than intended&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Overwatch Beta Patch Notes - February 18, 2016</title><description>A new beta patch is now live. Read below to learn about the latest changes.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446649/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Feedback&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446651/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note that some changes may not be documented or described in full detail.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GENERAL:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Miscellaneous&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Completed a tuning pass for end-of-match commendations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Increased the cooldown on using Voice Lines&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HERO BALANCE CHANGES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bastion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Configuration: Recon&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maximum weapon spread decreased by 25%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Configuration: Sentry&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No longer gains any armor bonus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;All changes to bullet damage made in our February 9 beta patch have been reverted&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: Weve given Configuration: Recon a bit of a boost to allow Bastion to run-and-gun more efficiently when needed. Weve also made significant changes to Bastions survivability and offensive capabilities when in Configuration: Sentry. By removing the 300 additional armor, Bastion is now more vulnerable to attack; however, its overall damage output has been increased (as a result of reverting earlier nerfs to sentry bullet damage). Were very eager to see how both of these updates play out in the beta. &lt;/em&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;D.Va&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;D.Vas mech is no longer move- or aim-locked after being called down&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Self-Destruct&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ultimate charge now generates passively even when D.Va is dead or her mech is destroyed&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Call Mech&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ultimate cost decreased by 20%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: The changes we made to how heroes gain Ultimate charge in the February 9 beta patch had some unintended side effects for D.Va, making it much harder for her to generate Ultimate than before. These changes should help correct this pain point, as well as provide a nice quality-of-life change to the process of summoning her mech. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mei&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Endothermic Blaster&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Alternate Fire&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ammo cost decreased from 50 to 40&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: The goal of this small change is make it so that using Meis alternate fire doesnt feel like its compromising her primary fire.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mercy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Guardian Angel&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Can no longer target the souls of dead allies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: The change we made to Guardian Angel in the February 9 beta patch (allowing the ability to target the souls of dead allies) was intended to help Mercy get to where her Resurrect may be the most needed. In practice, this change caused problems. We saw a lot of feedback from players noting that theyd accidentally target a dead ally when they meant to target a living ally, or that theyd target a dead ally thinking it was a living ally initially. As a result, weve reverted the original change. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Torbjrn&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Turret bullet damage decreased from 16 to 14&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Turret repair amount decreased from 100 to 50 health per swing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rivet Gun&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maximum ammo decreased from 20 to 18&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Alternate Fire&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cost decreased from 5 to 3&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Developer comments: Torbjrns turrets currently feel a little too powerful, so (to start) were taking away some of their power as well as removing Torbjrns ability to out-repair reasonable incoming damage. Torbjrns Rivet gun is also getting a small boost to allow for more liberal use of his Alternate Fire when needed.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BUG FIXES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed several in-game locations in which it was possible to use Tracers Blink ability to exit intended play space&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue when blue-colored effects would sometimes get stuck on screen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a crash that could happen when opening Loot Boxes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed several client- and sever-side crashes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heroes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused Zenyatta to receive more credit than intended for kill assists when determining Play of the Game&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spectating&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Projectiles will now appear to line up more correctly with targets when viewing a player in Spectator Mode&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Overwatch Beta Patch Notes - February 16, 2016</title><description>A new beta patch is now live. Read below to learn about the latest changes.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446649/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Feedback&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446651/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note that some changes may not be documented or described in full detail.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;span class="underline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BUG FIXES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Highlight Intros will now correctly randomize for all heroes (instead of just Tracer) whenever the Random option is selected in the Hero Gallery&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that would cause the game to crash when playing randomized Highlight Intros for Tracer&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue with stats wrapping on the end-of-round progression screen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed several client- and server-side crashes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maps&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Updated several in-game locations and objects on Nepal and Lijiang Tower to prevent players from being able to reach, stand, and/or get stuck on them&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed several lighting issues on Lijiang Tower&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spectating&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spectators will now automatically move on to the next part of the map at the end of each round when spectating Control games&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed several issues with inconsistent or incorrect team coloring while spectating&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused projectiles to appear too far in front of the weapon that fired them while spectating &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Overwatch Beta Patch Notes - February 9, 2016</title><description>A new beta patch is now live. Read below to learn about the latest changes.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446649/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Feedback&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446651/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Table of Contents:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20742184292#post-2" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Patch Features&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20742184292#post-3" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;General&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20742184292#post-4" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Hero Balance Changes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20742184292#post-5" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;User Interface&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/20742184292#post-6" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Bug Fixes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note that some changes may not be documented or described in full detail.</description></item><item><title>Developer Update | Beta is Back!</title><description>With the return of Closed Beta, we're happy to share &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=41DLNBzp68Q" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;another developer&lt;/a&gt; update featuring Game Director, Jeff Kaplan. This edition covers details regarding what the team has been working on while the Closed Beta has been offline. You'll get an introduction to loot boxes, a synopsis of the new game mode and a recap of how Private Game evolved into Custom Game. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As always, give it a watch and share you're feedback, we're in this together!</description></item><item><title>Closed Beta Update - January 21, 2016</title><description>Happy 2016 Everyone!&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Its been a while since weve chatted, so I wanted to provide a quick update on the status of the Overwatch Closed Beta.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;When we brought the Closed Beta offline last December, we did so with the intent to use the downtime to address player feedback, work on some core features (&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rnkF7hdUYhU" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;like progression!&lt;/a&gt;), and adjust the balance of the game. Our goal was to have all of that work completed before bringing the Closed Beta back online, and our hope was to have that goal complete by middle to late January.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;While progress has been great and the team has been working super hard to get everything implemented on time, we're not quite ready to bring the Closed Beta back online just yet. Weve been pretty open about the fact that we could slip into February from the beginning, but a big reason for this delay is that we really wanted to add one more big feature to the next beta patch. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;After looking through all of the feedback from last year, one of the things we noticed players consistently mentioning was their desire for more game modes in Overwatch, in addition to Point Capture and Payload. Without getting into specifics, we are working on a new game mode. And were very excited about it! And we have some great new maps to support it, too, but we need a little more time to get everything just right.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Rather than try to rush a beta patch out this month (which would mean the new game mode would have to be put off), were going to take a few extra weeks before bringing the Closed Beta back. By doing so, we can make sure we can include the new game mode along with the new maps. This will also allow us to do some additional polish to the games progression and reward system. Though all these features will still technically be a work-in-progress during the beta, wed like them to be at a certain quality bar before releasing them for testing. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;This was an easy choice for us to make, and hopefully this post can help you understand why we made it. I dont have an exact date for when the Closed Beta will resume, but right now were looking at mid-February (and we dont intend to slip out of February). Well do our best to provide at least one weeks notice before were ready to get this beta party started again, so definitely keep an eye on our official channels. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;We love making this game with you guys. Its been so much fun and youve been incredibly supportive of us. Thank you all so much for your patience and we hope to see you in-game soon!</description></item><item><title>Developer Update | Popular Community Topics</title><description>Our most recent &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OKG8Yx6F7uc&amp;amp;feature=youtu.be" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;update&lt;/a&gt; features Game Director Jeff Kaplan as he discusses some popular community topics including current plans for additional heroes and maps post-launch, updates regarding an in-game killfeed and scoreboard, and other minor changes coming as a result of player feedback. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you have something you'd like us to cover in a future update, feel free to post a comment on YouTube or reach out to us on Twitter at @PlayOverwatch. Thanks for watching!</description></item><item><title>Overwatch Beta Patch Notes - December 2, 2015</title><description>A new beta patch is now live. Read below to learn about the latest changes.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446649/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Feedback&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446651/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BUG FIXES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where Mei's Ice Wall was able to destroy Torbjrn's turrets&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that allowed Tracer to escape team spawn rooms by recalling to the top of a destroyed Ice Wall before the match had begun&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that allowed players to escape the attacking teams spawn room on Kings Row before the match had begun&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where a player's Voice Chat icon would sometimes appear grayed out even if they were active in the channel &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused players Battle.net Friends Lists to be reset whenever automatically silenced in Overwatch&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed several client- and server-side crashes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Stress Test Weekend: Thank You!</title><description>Hi Everyone,&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;On behalf of the Overwatch Team, I wanted to thank you all for helping to test out Overwatch this past weekend. We know you have so many ways to spend your free time so choosing to help us test out OW and make the game better really means the world to us. The feedback and suggestions that you all provided were so thoughtful and were eager to make the game better based on your input. We were doing a lot of experiments that might have created some bumpy moments along the way but you all were super patient with us and kept right on testing.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Also, it was just tons of fun playing alongside of you all. The team was playing all weekend. In theory, we were testing the service to make sure everything was working smoothly. In reality, we were having a blast teaming with you all and fighting the good fight.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As Tracer said in our announcement cinematic, The world could always use more heroes. You all were those heroes for us this weekend.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Many thanks,&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Overwatch Team</description></item><item><title>Scheduled Beta Maintenance - November 23, 2015</title><description>&lt;strong&gt;UPDATE:&lt;/strong&gt; Maintenance for Overwatch has completed at this time and is available for Closed Beta participants! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;--------------------&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATE:&lt;/strong&gt; Maintenance has been extended. We don't have an ETA to share at this time, but will provide another update once the beta is live. Thanks for your patience!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;--------------------&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Following the conclusion of our first Beta Test Weekend on Monday, November 23 at 9:00 AM PST (6:00 PM CET), we will be bringing down the Overwatch beta for scheduled maintenance. We expect this maintenance to be relatively short and for the beta to be available again at approximately 2:00 PM PST (11:00 PM CET).&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;For beta status updates, please follow &lt;a href="http://www.twitter.com/PlayOverwatch" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;@PlayOverwatch&lt;/a&gt; on Twitter.&lt;br/&gt;For more information about the Beta Test Weekend, &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/overwatch/en/blog/19964704/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;.</description></item><item><title>Possible Interruptions - November 22, 2015</title><description>As part of our Beta Test Weekend, we will be performing some tests on our hardware beginning on Sunday, November 22 at 11:00 AM PST until around 3:30 PM PST. During this time, players may experience brief interruptions of service including disconnects. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We want to thank you again for helping us test Overwatch and apologize for any inconvenience.</description></item><item><title>Clarification Re: Closed Beta vs. Beta Test Weekend</title><description>Hey all,&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;We've seen some confusion from players who've recently had their account flagged for the Overwatch beta not knowing which type of invite they received: Beta Test Weekend or Closed Beta.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;We sincerely apologize for this confusion and hope to provide some clarity.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you've been invited to the Beta Test Weekend:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You will see an "Install" button in the Overwatch tab of the Battle.net desktop app&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You will see an "Overwatch Beta" license in Account Management&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You will receive an email titled "Play the Overwatch Beta This Weekend!" &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You will be able to post in the following forums beginning Friday around 9:00 a.m. PST:&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/21446646/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Stress Test Feedback&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/21882797/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Stress Test Tech Support&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/21882798/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Stress Test Bug Report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you've been invited to the Closed Beta:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You will see an "Install" button in the Overwatch tab of the Battle.net desktop app&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You will see an "Overwatch Beta" license in Account Management&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You will receive an email titled "Welcome to the Overwatch Closed Beta!" &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You will be able to post in the following forums immediately:&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/21446649/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Feedback&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/21446650/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Tech Support&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/21446651/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Bug Report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Your feedback on this whole process has been greatly appreciated, and were already taking steps to make improvements for the future. (For example, we recognize that having Account Management display separate licenses for Closed Beta and Beta Test Weekends would have made it easier for players to see which type of invite they received.)&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;In the meantime, thank you to everyone who's able to help us stress test our hardware this weekend. We also hope youll take some time to share your thoughts and experiences here in our official forums.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;For more information about this Beta Test Weekend, &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/overwatch/en/blog/19964704/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;For more information about Closed Beta,&lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/overwatch/en/blog/19932055/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt; click here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;* Notification emails can sometimes take several hours to arrive.&lt;/em&gt;</description></item><item><title>Overwatch Beta Patch Notes - November 20, 2015</title><description>A new beta patch is now live. Read below to learn about the latest changes.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446649/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Feedback&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446651/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GENERAL:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Rate This Player UI now clearly indicates which options are Negative, Neutral, or Positive&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HERO BALANCE CHANGES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/overwatch/en/heroes/genji/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Genji&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Swift Strike&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Impact damage has been slightly increased&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Damage-over-time effect has been removed&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/overwatch/en/heroes/mei/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Mei&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Blizzard&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mei can no longer gain ultimate charge while Blizzard is active&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/overwatch/en/heroes/mercy/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Mercy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Caduceus Staff&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Damage Boost Beam&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Damage bonus has been reduced  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;li&gt;Resurrect&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Effect now happens at the start of the cast time, instead of the end&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Note: We are reverting the change to Resurrect made in our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/topic/19865536388" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;November 9 patch  &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/overwatch/en/heroes/widowmaker/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Widowmaker&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Widow's Kiss&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Scoped shot damage has been slightly reduced&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Scoped shots will now consume 3 bullets instead of 1&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Overwatch Beta Patch Notes - November 18, 2015</title><description>A new beta patch is now live. Read below to learn about the latest changes.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446649/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Feedback&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446651/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GENERAL:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Players will no longer see their own real name displayed whenever they speak in chat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;BattleTag numeric IDs will no longer display in chat whenever a player joins or leaves Voice Chat  &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Made several additional improvements to matchmaking&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HERO BALANCE CHANGES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/overwatch/en/heroes/mei/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Mei&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;If multiple Meis are attacking the same target, their freeze effects will no longer stack&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BUG FIXES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue where some players werent able to use microphones with Voice Chat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed several client-side crashes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Developer Update | Matchmaking &amp;amp; Hero Balance</title><description>The latest update from Overwatch Game Director Jeff Kaplan can be found &lt;a href="https://youtu.be/04a7Mv_eWdY " class="bml-link-url2"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This vlog covers some of the recent patch updates from 11/17, including explanations about the "Rate this Match" and "Rate this Player" features. You'll also hear some of the thoughts behind hero balance changes and what defense heroes may have adjustments coming next year.</description></item><item><title>Overwatch Beta Patch Notes - November 17, 2015</title><description>A new beta patch is now live. Read below to learn about the latest changes.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446649/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Feedback&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446651/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PATCH HIGHLIGHTS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;This patch includes several changes to the in-game matchmaker. These changes are in large part an experiment, aimed at achieving two main goals: &lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1)&lt;/strong&gt; Provide players with better, more balanced matches overall (short term)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2)&lt;/strong&gt; Generate data that will allow us to make even further improvements (long term) &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As with many experiments, however, we may find that these changes arent whats best for the gameor, in some cases, may even make your experience worseso we encourage you to share your thoughts and opinions in our forums.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Matchmaking Changes:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;New "Rate This Match" and "Rate This Player" options have been added to the end-of-round flow&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rate This Match: These ratings are designed to provide the Overwatch development team with feedback about how much you enjoyed a match. This data will be used over time to improve matchmaking and the game in general.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rate This Player: Positive and negative ratings can have an effect on how likely players are to be matched with one another in future games.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Several behind-the-scenes improvements have been made to the in-game matchmaker, especially for groups&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Refined some of the language that appears on-screen when searching for a match&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ex: Instead of "X of Y Players Found," players will now see "Estimated Time" and "Elapsed Time" counters&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GENERAL:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A new loading screen is now available when loading into a Skirmish&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Skirmish timer has been increased to 30 minutes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BUG FIXES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that would sometimes cause the Play of the Game recap to feature the wrong portion of the match when received by D.Va&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Scheduled Beta Maintenance - November 19, 2015</title><description>&lt;strong&gt;UPDATE:&lt;/strong&gt; Maintenance for Overwatch has concluded. Enjoy the Beta Test Weekend!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;--------------------&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In preparation for our upcoming Beta Test Weekend, we will be bringing down the Overwatch beta on Thursday, November 19 around 10:00 AM PST (7:00 PM CET) for scheduled maintenance. We expect this maintenance to last a little less than 24 hours and the beta to be available again on Friday, November 20 at approximately 9:00 AM PST (6:00 PM CET). &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For beta status updates, please follow &lt;a href="http://www.twitter.com/PlayOverwatch" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;@PlayOverwatch&lt;/a&gt; on Twitter.&lt;br/&gt;For more information about the Beta Test Weekend, &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/overwatch/en/blog/19964704/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;.</description></item><item><title>Overwatch Beta Patch Notes - November 9, 2015</title><description>A new beta patch is now live. Read below to learn about the latest changes.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446649/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Feedback&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446651/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PATCH HIGHLIGHTS: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;New Hero added: &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/overwatch/en/heroes/dva" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;D.Va &lt;/a&gt;(Tank)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;New Hero added: &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/overwatch/en/heroes/genji" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Genji&lt;/a&gt; (Offense)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;New Hero added: &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/overwatch/en/heroes/mei" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Mei &lt;/a&gt;(Defense)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;New Map added: &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/overwatch/en/game/#objectives" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Hollywood&lt;/a&gt; (Point Capture/Payload Hybrid)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HERO BALANCE CHANGES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/overwatch/en/heroes/mercy/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Mercy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Resurrection - Effect now happens at the end of the cast time, instead of the start&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/overwatch/en/heroes/mccree/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;McCree&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Peacekeeper - Damage is now reduced at long ranges&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Deadeye - Duration significantly reduced&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/overwatch/en/heroes/pharah/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Pharah&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rocket Launcher - Rate of fire has been slightly reduced&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/overwatch/en/heroes/symmetra/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Symmetra&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Photon Shield - Cooldown has been significantly reduced&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sentry Turret - Cooldown has been significantly reduced&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/overwatch/en/heroes/widowmaker/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Widowmaker&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Infra-Sight - Widowmaker can no longer gain ultimate charge while Infra-Sight is active&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BUG FIXES: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a bug that would sometimes prevent Junkrats RIP-Tire VO from playing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed several bugs that allowed Reaper to enter or exit enemy team spawn rooms&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed several client-side crashes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Overwatch Beta Patch Notes - November 3, 2015</title><description>A new beta patch is now live. Read below to learn about the latest changes.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446649/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Feedback&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446651/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BUG FIXES:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;li&gt;Updated several in-game locations and objects to prevent players from being able to reach, stand, and/or get stuck on them&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Updated several in-game objects so that Reaper can no longer Teleport through or into them unexpectedly &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The "invalid hardware or driver detected" window can now be bypassed&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed an issue that caused the Muted Microphone UI element to disappear whenever the Channels menu was open&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed several reliability issues with Voice Chat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed several client- and server-side crashes&lt;/li&gt;</description></item><item><title>Overwatch Beta Patch Notes - October 30, 2015</title><description>A new beta patch is now live. Read below to learn about the latest changes.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;To share your feedback, please post in the &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446649/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Feedback&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt;For a list of known issues, visit our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en-us/overwatch/21446651/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Bug Report&lt;/a&gt; forum.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GENERAL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;li&gt;Aim assist for gamepad controllers has been disabled&lt;/li&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BUG FIXES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fixed a number of client-side crashes&lt;/li&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Please note that, due to a file format change, this patch will be approximately 1GB.</description></item><item><title>Developer Update | Welcome to Beta!</title><description>Overwatch Game Director Jeff Kaplan discusses expectations and goal of the Overwatch beta in this &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PnRpV4V5H0w" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;vlog&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We encourage everyone to take a few minutes and watch this personal video that shares some insights about the design process and what you may encounter as you engage with the beta.</description></item><item><title>Scheduled Maintenance (EU) - October 27, 2015</title><description>&lt;strong&gt;UPDATE:&lt;/strong&gt; Maintenance for Overwatch in EU has completed early, and is available for play! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;--------------------&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATE:&lt;/strong&gt; Maintenance for the Europe gameplay region will now begin on Wednesday, October 28 at 12:00 AM CET and last approximately 8 hours, concluding at approximately 08:00 AM CET.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;--------------------&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We will be performing scheduled maintenance beginning on Wednesday, October 28, at 1:00 AM CET (5:00 PM PT) and expect the service to be available again at approximately 6:00 AM CET (10:00 PM PT). During this time, the Overwatch beta will be unavailable in the Europe gameplay region.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please follow &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/BlizzardCS" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;@BlizzardCS&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/BlizzardCSEU_EN" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;BlizzardCSEU_EN&lt;/a&gt; on Twitter for further updates.</description></item><item><title>Overwatch Closed Beta FAQ</title><description>&lt;strong&gt;Q. How can I opt-in to the Overwatch Closed Beta?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To opt into the beta, visit your &lt;a href="https://us.battle.net/account/management/beta-profile.html" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Profile Settings&lt;/a&gt; page in Account Management, check the "Overwatch" box under "Beta Tests I'm Interested In," and then click "Update Preferences." Alternatively, you can also sign up by clicking &lt;a href="http://blizz.ly/JoinOverwatch" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Please note that opting in will not guarantee you access to the Closed Beta.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. How are Closed Beta participants selected?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Beta testers are chosen based on many factors, including your Battle.net region, when you signed up, your computer hardware specifications, and an element of luck. We are also inviting select journalists and community contributors from around the world on a case-by-case basis.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. How will I know if I'm selected to participate in the Closed Beta?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you are selected to participate in the Closed Beta, you will receive an invite via email. Invites will always be sent to the email address associated with your Battle.net account.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;To help avoid phishing attempts, if you believe you've received an invite, it's best to refrain from clicking on any links in the email(s) you receive. Instead, you can verify that your account has been granted a Closed Beta license in &lt;a href="https://us.battle.net/account/management/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Battle.net Account Management&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. Will there be any other ways to get into the Closed Beta besides opting-in?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Not at this time. Also, please note that Overwatch beta keys do not exist. Access to the Closed Beta will be provided solely through account flagging.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. How many players do you plan to invite to the Closed Beta?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The number of players we invite will be largely based on our testing needs. We also want to make sure the games matchmaking system remains in a relatively healthy place throughout this phase of testing.  As a result, if we determine we need more players to test new features or keep matches running smoothly, well continue to add people to the Closed Beta from our opt-in pool.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. What gameplay regions is the Closed Beta available in?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Closed Beta is currently available in the Americas and Europe gameplay regions. We have plans to bring the beta to our Asia gameplay region at a later date. For more information on which countries are associated with each of our gameplay regions, &lt;a href="https://us.battle.net/support/en/article/global-play" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Game performance for players in some regions, such as Australia, New Zealand, Southeast Asia, and Central and South America may be sub-optimal during the beta. If you experience issues with gameplay like high latency, excessive loading times, or long matchmaking queues, please be sure to post in our &lt;a href="http://us.battle.net/forums/en/overwatch/" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;beta forums&lt;/a&gt; so that we can work to make improvements. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. What languages are supported in the Closed Beta?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Closed Beta currently supports 10 languages: English, French, German, Castilian Spanish, Polish, Italian, Russian, Latin American Spanish, and Brazilian Portuguese. Localization is not yet complete for all languages, however, so some content may still appear in English during the beta.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. If I get invited to the Closed Beta, can I stream or create content about the game?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Absolutely! There is no non-disclosure agreement (NDA) for the Closed Beta. You are encouraged to take screenshots, livestream your play sessions, record feedback videoswhatever your heart desires. The game is still a work in progress, though, so we appreciate your understanding when you encounter bugs, graphical errors, or other issues.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. Can I run tournaments with a prize pool during the Closed Beta?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Yes! You are welcome to run tournaments (with or without prize pools) during the Closed Beta. However, given the size and scope of this phase of beta, we will not be issuing tournament licenses for large-scale events with prize pools over $10k. For smaller events, please review our &lt;a href="http://wcs.battle.net/sc2/en/about/community-tournaments" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Community Tournament Guidelines&lt;/a&gt; before you begin planning to make sure your community tournament is in compliance. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;If you would like to begin discussing your tournament plans for after game launch, or have any other questions, feel free to reach out to  tourneyinfo@blizzard.com. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. How long will the Closed Beta last?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This phase of the Closed Beta will conclude before the end of the year. We dont have an exact date to share at this time, but well be sure to provide testers with advanced notice.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. Will any progress I make during the Closed Beta carry over to the live game?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;No. Weve no plans at this time for your activity during the Closed Beta to carry over. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. If I dont get into the Closed Beta, am I guaranteed access to a Beta Test Weekend?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;No. While Beta Test Weekends will include a much larger number of players than Closed Beta, they will also be invite-only. Youll need to opt-in to the Overwatch beta to be eligible.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. How do I opt-in to the Beta Test Weekends?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;There is no special opt-in process for Beta Test Weekends. If you opted-in for the beta, youre all set!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As a reminder: To opt into the beta, visit your &lt;a href="https://us.battle.net/account/management/beta-profile.html" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;Beta Profile Settings&lt;/a&gt; page in Account Management, check the "Overwatch" box under "Beta Tests I'm Interested In," and then click "Update Preferences." Alternatively, you can also sign up by clicking &lt;a href="http://blizz.ly/JoinOverwatch" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Again, please note that opting in will not guarantee you access to a Beta Test Weekend.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. What are the system requirements for the Closed Beta?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;See below!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Minimum (targeting 30fps):&lt;br/&gt;&amp;gt;Operating system: Windows Vista/7/ 8/10 64-bit (latest Service Pack) &lt;br/&gt;&amp;gt;Processor: Intel Core i3 or AMD Phenom X3 865&lt;br/&gt;&amp;gt;Video: NVIDIA GeForce GTX 460, ATI Radeon HD 4850, or Intel HD Graphics 4400&lt;br/&gt;&amp;gt;Memory: 768 MB VRAM, 4 GB System RAM &lt;br/&gt;&amp;gt;Storage: 7200 RPM with 5 GB available HD space &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Recommended (targeting 60fps on Medium settings):&lt;br/&gt;&amp;gt; Operating system: Windows Vista/7/ 8/10 64-bit (latest Service Pack) &lt;br/&gt;&amp;gt; Processor: Intel Core i5 or AMD Phenom II X3, 2.8 GHz&lt;br/&gt;&amp;gt; Video: NVIDIA GeForce GTX 660 or ATI Radeon HD 7950&lt;br/&gt;&amp;gt; Memory: 2 GB VRAM, 6 GB System RAM &lt;br/&gt;&amp;gt; Storage: 7200 RPM with 5 GB available HD space &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;For the best performance, please be sure to update to the latest drivers available for your graphics card.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. Will Mac users be able to participate in the beta?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Were developing Overwatch for Windows-based PCs only, so a Mac-specific beta will not be provided.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. What is the business model for Overwatch?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Overwatch is currently available for pre-purchase on Windows PC, PlayStation 4, and Xbox One. For more information, visit &lt;a href="http://www.buyoverwatch.com" class="bml-link-url2"&gt;www.buyoverwatch.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q. When will the game be released?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Overwatch is set to release in Spring 2016.</description></item></channel></rss>